CRIME SCENE ZERO
Today, 583 more people
have tested positive for COVID-19.
The government has raised the level
of social distancing and banned gatherings
of more than five people...
Tonight, Seoul City is introducing
a citywide shutdown of shops after 9 p.m.,
sending a strong message to the public.
WHOLE CHICKIN
Breaking news.
Record-breaking heavy rain has caused
severe flooding in the central region...
Especially in the Gangdam District,
where hourly rainfall of 120 mm
has caused flooding in many areas...
Gangdam District
is working to minimize damage
by monitoring precipitation in real time
and closing vulnerable roads.
GANGDAM DISTRICT
CLOSES ROADS TO MINIMIZE DAMAGE
NO ENTRY
DETOUR ADVISED DUE TO ROAD FLOOD
AUGUST 12, 2020, 12:00 A.M.
It's the perfect weather
for a crime to occur.
Jeez.
What a cruel and chaotic world.
SELF TEMPERATURE CHECK
Normal.
PASSED
LEAD INVESTIGATOR ON THE FOURTH CASE
JANG DETECTIVE
Oh boy.
GANGDAM DISTRICT
TEMPORARY SCREENING CENTER
"SOCIAL DISTANCING MEASURES" FOR COVID-19
COMBINED WITH UNPRECEDENTED HEAVY RAIN
UNUSUALLY QUIET YOUTH STREET
NEAR GANGDAM STATION
THE VICTIM'S LIFELESS BODY
WAS FOUND AT THE HEART OF IT
MURDER IN THE NIGHTLIFE DISTRICT I
How could a murder like this
have happened in the heart of Gangdam?
How does this make any sense?
- Hey!
- Detective.
Hello, sir. AD, reporting for duty.
Get over here.
Who knows what kind of germs
you might be carrying?
- Okay, you can take off your mask.
- Got it.
NO GERMS TO TRANSMIT
ASSISTANT DETECTIVE
KANG MINHEE
Detective, don't tell me you caught it.
(THOROUGH)
What were you up to
before becoming an assistant detective?
I used to dance a little.
- You danced?
- Yes.
- Is that so?
Show me some moves, then.
I need to see whether you'll make
a decent assistant detective or not.
Got it.
WARMING UP HIS JOINTS...
ACK!
A RAIN-SOAKED HAZING
That was part of my performance.
That was some impressive dancing.
VERY SATISFIED
I approve. You pass.
THE ASSISTANT DETECTIVE
TITLE EARNED THROUGH PAIN
Anyway, what case are we dealing with?
What happened here?
To be honest, I had trouble
identifying the victim for today's case.
All I know is
she worked at Sensibility Bar--
What?
So we don't have anything else
on the victim?
At the moment, we don't.
Are you kidding me?
Fine. Do we at least have our suspects?
Yes, sir. I'll bring them all here.
- Put the squeeze on them first.
- Yes, sir.
They should be taught
who's the boss from the get-go.
A VICTIM DIFFICULT TO IDENTIFY...
That weather's awful.
WHO ARE THE SUSPECTS IN THIS CASE?
Any idea why we got called out this late?
What's the holdup? Move it along!
- Don't you know gatherings are banned?
- Suspects.
Suspects, form a single line.
- Keep in mind the times we're in.
- Who are you calling a suspect?
Who are you to boss us around?
I'm the lead detective on this case.
- A case?
- In light of the pandemic,
- I'll check your temperature first.
- Sure.
THOROUGH TEMPERATURE CHECK
You're at 36.3°C.
- Pass. You may remove your mask.
- Thanks.
- Wait here.
- What?
- Stand by!
- Okay.
Repeat the command. Stand by.
Stand by!
You're at 36.4°C. Pass.
Jeez. What's with all this nonsense?
You're at 36.3°C. Pass.
Did you even sanitize this?
- Pick up the pace.
- You're at 36.3°C.
- What the...
- What a hassle.
Are you serious right now?
It's because of the pandemic.
I've been flipping this mask inside out
every three days to get by.
I have no choice but to target your eye.
A NECESSARY ACTION
You're at 36.5°C. Pass.
- But my eyes are intense.
- I'm a busy person, you know.
- What the heck is going on?
- Why are we here?
- All right.
- I've been out all day today.
There's been a murder.
- What?
- Let's take a look at the crime scene.
It's this way. Come with me.
- Who in the world died?
- Seems like I'm tangled up in a mess.
- What is this?
- Who is this?
Is that Gun-mi?
Gun-mi?
- What the heck?
- Is that Gun-mi?
- Gun-mi?
- It's Lee Gun-mi.
- Gun-mi!
- Gun-mi?
- It's Lee Gun-mi.
- Hold on.
Do you know the victim?
Gun-mi's my friend.
- Gun-mi? What's her last name?
- Yes.
- Lee Gun-mi.
- Lee Gun-mi?
You know the victim, Ms. Lee Gun-mi?
FRIENDS WITH THE VICTIM?
Hold on.
Since she's your friend,
can I assume she's a woman?
Anyone can tell she's a woman.
Let's move things along.
You say she's a woman, but...
Her neck... Oh jeez!
What's wrong?
She has an Adam's apple.
Look.
What?
What the heck?
Detective!
Hey, AD.
Here's the victim's file.
HAS THE VICTIM FINALLY BEEN IDENTIFIED?
Is that the case? I see.
The victim is Lee Gun-jun.
What?
A 27-year-old male.
Are you saying that's Lee Gun-jun,
not Lee Gun-mi?
THE VICTIM ISN'T LEE GUN-MI, A WOMAN,
BUT LEE GUN-JUN, A MAN?
Wait. Gun-jun's my friend.
HIS FRIEND?
Are you saying this is Gun-jun?
Didn't you hear the detective say
he was 27, you old man?
How old are you?
Just so you know, I'm 27.
He's my friend, and we're the same age.
The world is going mad, isn't it?
Come on, Ms. Park. Don't be like that.
I can tell something's off
about you people already.
The victim is Lee Gun-jun,
a 27-year-old male.
Unemployed.
His body was discovered
in the nightlife district
of Gangdam Station's Youth Street
at midnight on the 12th.
Exposure to the rain caused inconsistency
in the rate
at which the body temperature dropped,
making it impossible
to accurately determine the time of death.
The rain not only made it difficult
to estimate the time of death
but also wiped away the victim's blood
and potential evidence
left behind by the culprit.
This puts us in a very tough spot.
Business was already bad around here,
and now this?
Bad luck just doesn't let up, does it?
- Let's catch who did it.
- Form a single line and follow me.
Don't you dare slip away and come with me.
I need to get back to the store.
DIGGING INTO THE SUSPECTS
We're in for a ride today.
First suspect, Kim Club.
A 57-year-old male.
Owner of Club Slam.
Second suspect, An Dancer.
A 27-year-old female.
Dancer at Club Slam.
Third suspect, Park Chicken.
A 38-year-old female.
Owner of a fried chicken restaurant.
Fourth suspect, Jang C-store.
A 27-year-old male.
Part-timer at a convenience store.
Fifth suspect, Ha Gold Spoon.
A 32-year-old male.
Attorney and mediator
of the Gangdam District lease dispute.
Let's hurry up and catch the culprit
so the victim's soul can find peace
after the wrongful death.
- Got it?
- Who knows if it was wrongful?
All right. Let's begin the investigation.
The first thing we need to clarify
is whether you knew the victim
as Lee Gun-mi or Lee Gun-jun.
That's crucial.
- Mr. Kim Club.
- Yes?
Please introduce yourself
and how you knew the victim.
Sure thing.
I'm the owner of the hottest club
near Gangdam Station in Gangdam District.
- It's called Club Slam.
-"Club Slam"?
- I run a club near Gangdam Station.
- Okay.
The victim, did you say?
Yes.
Lee Gun-mi, was it?
The victim's name was Lee Gun-jun,
not Lee Gun-mi.
That darn brat was a guy.
Are you saying
you didn't know he was a man?
I thought he was a she.
So you had no idea
that the victim was a man?
How would I have known that?
Understood.
We'll move on to Ms. Park Chicken.
Right. Well, I've been running
a fried chicken restaurant
for just over a year now.
- A year?
- That's right.
I knew the victim as Lee Gun-mi,
and we've been friends for several years.
So you and Ms. Lee Gun-mi were friends?
We used to keep in touch regularly,
but then drifted apart.
- We only recently reconnected.
- Hold on.
Ms. Park is one scary woman.
Wait. Are those tattoos on your arms?
Yes. Is having tattoos against the law?
Do you slaughter the chickens yourself?
Why is your apron covered in blood?
I'm all about serving fried chicken
from freshly butchered chickens.
My restaurant is pretty well-known
around Gangdam District.
Do you always wear your hair like that
while frying chicken?
- Got a problem with it?
- Are those horns or what?
My customers say
they look like drumsticks,
but it's actually for hygiene.
The fried chicken lady
with the drumstick hairstyle.
Let's move on to Mr. Ha Gold Spoon.
- Sure thing.
- Please go ahead.
Honestly, I don't even know why I'm here.
- I save lives, not take them away.
- He's hot.
- Isn't he super hot?
- Is that so?
I'm working as the mediator
of the Gangdam District
commercial property lease dispute.
However, my main job is an attorney.
My family members
have practiced law for generations,
so I naturally chose the same path.
Hey, Detective. Let's send this guy home.
- Yes, let's.
- He couldn't have done this.
That's for me to decide!
Gold Spoon's not the type
to be in this part of town.
- He's on the suspect list.
- Did you call him by name?
Did I hear that right?
Are you on a first-name basis?
- Look here.
- Mr. Gold Spoon.
Is that how things are?
I serve the public, so why am I here
being treated like a criminal?
- I can vouch for this man.
- Right.
He's actually my landlord.
- Everyone around here knows him.
- In Gangdam District...
Are you a landlord?
I sure am. Goldspoon Buildings 1 and 2
are registered in my name.
I see, sir.
(SUDDENLY SHOWING RESPECT)
I'll do my best
to make you comfortable today.
Do you need an office?
Well, kind of.
- I'll let you know if a spot opens up.
- Sure.
Anyway,
did you know the victim,
either as Lee Gun-jun or Lee Gun-mi?
I went to Sensibility Bar to grab a drink
by myself and met the victim,
who was working part-time.
- That's when we got to know each other.
- Sensibility Bar?
Was the victim working part-time
as Lee Gun-jun or Lee Gun-mi?
She was working there as Lee Gun-mi.
Lee Gun-mi worked part-time.
- And that's how you met her?
- That's right.
I'm shocked
by what Ms. Chicken, Mr. Club,
- and Mr. Attorney just said.
- Why's that?
Because that's definitely Gun-jun,
my classmate from high school.
- What?
- Yeah.
What are you on about?
I can't believe
he's been living as a woman,
partying and working part-time.
I'm just so shocked
by everything I've just heard.
I had absolutely no idea.
Anyway, I work part-time
at a local convenience store.
My name's Jang C-store.
You might know this already,
but I work longer hours
than most part-timers.
I see him at the store whenever I drop by.
- He's very hardworking.
- Very.
Morning, evening, or night.
He's always there.
Judging by his looks,
I thought he was the owner.
Just to avoid any misunderstandings,
I really am 27.
- You seem like a nice guy.
- We're the same age.
Keep reminding us
so we won't get confused.
- We're the same age.
- This is a crazy world.
You must find it easy
to speak casually to him, then.
Why would I be uncomfortable
when we're the same age, Gold Spoon?
Since you're talking,
we'll move on to you, Ms. An Dancer.
Okay. I'm An Dancer, Gun-mi's best friend.
Mr. Kim Club is my boss.
I work as a dancer at his club.
- She's one of my employees.
- At Club Slam?
You said you were friends
with the victim, Ms. Lee Gun-mi.
Yes, we were best friends.
To be honest, I knew.
Knew what?
I knew she was actually a guy.
- What?
- You knew?
You became best friends with Lee Gun-mi
despite knowing she was actually a guy?
We were best friends from the beginning.
We were close enough
that we eventually shared our secrets.
She told me herself.
Did the victim want to transition
to become a woman?
Yes, she was a woman at heart.
A woman at heart, huh?
Yes.
We couldn't get an accurate read
on the victim's body temperature
due to exposure to the heavy rain.
And that means, we can't pin down
the estimated time of death.
Oh dear.
I'd like to know the last time
each of you saw the victim,
either as Lee Gun-jun or Lee Gun-mi.
I didn't see him.
Were you working
at the convenience store yesterday?
- I was.
- You were on shift,
but you didn't notice anything going on
in the empty lot next to the store?
No, and just so you know,
Gun-jun lived above the convenience store.
- Yet, you didn't see him?
- No, I didn't see him yesterday.
- Are you sure?
- He could be lying.
That's rather suspicious.
What about you, Mr. Club?
I saw her around 8:20 p.m.
- Did you say 8:20 p.m.?
- It was around then. Yes.
Where did you see her?
In front of her place.
I see. So, you saw her.
What about you, ma'am?
I think it was a little over 9 p.m.
- I saw her outside her place.
- Outside her home?
You saw her outside her home.
What?
Ms. Chicken's account
just jogged my memory.
I saw them arguing at around 9:15 p.m.
We didn't meet up or anything.
I just happened to see it.
I'll take your word for now.
The truth will come out
once we investigate.
- That sounds suspicious.
- You'll be in big trouble if you lie.
What about you, sir?
I bumped into her briefly yesterday.
Around what time and where?
It was past 9 p.m...
Let me think.
It was around 9:45 p.m.
- Around 9:45?
- Where?
- Right here. Outside my office.
Outside your office?
She didn't come inside?
No, she didn't.
You ran into her outside your office.
How did she seem?
I can't recall the details,
but she seemed to be in a hurry.
In a hurry?
Ha Gold Spoon said he saw her at 9:45 p.m.
Isn't the last person
to see the victim alive
usually the most suspicious?
No one saw her after that
because she was dead by then.
Assuming you're all telling the truth,
the estimated time of death
is between 9:45 p.m. and midnight.
Now, please tell me
what you were doing during that time.
I'd appreciate full honesty.
I probably look
the most suspicious right now,
so I'll tell you
how my evening went first.
I was in a meeting with business owners
who were affected by COVID-19.
- A meeting?
- Yes, it was held right here.
- He's telling the truth.
- You can see the banner over there.
"Gangdam Station Youth Street Meeting
With Business Owners
Affected by COVID-19."
- You hosted that meeting?
- I did.
I personally secured the support fund
from the Gangdam District Head.
Hoping to be of some help
to business owners,
I used my gift of persuasion
on the District Head.
Okay, when did the meeting end?
I gave legal advice until midnight,
so my alibi is solid.
- So, you were in a meeting.
- That's right.
And you, Mr. Club?
I was here with my landlord.
After all,
I'm also a small local business owner.
- You attended the meeting?
- Yes, I arrived at around 9:30 p.m.
- Did you sign the document?
- Of course.
- And Ms. Dancer?
- I also went to the meeting
on behalf of the owner of Sensibility Bar.
Was the whole neighborhood there or what?
You had to attend to receive aid.
NO SUPPORT FUND FOR ABSENTEES
Dancer's one of my employees,
but something came up
for the owner of Sensibility Bar,
so I brought her along to the meeting
so she could represent them.
Understood.
What about you, kid?
Can you also call me by my name,
Detective?
- I want to be called by my name.
- Do you?
The more I see him,
the younger he appears.
- C-store.
- Yes?
What were you up to?
I was also at the meeting.
- You were at the meeting too?
- Yes.
- I also--
- What about your shift?
I got here after my shift, so I was late.
In that case, Ms. Chicken,
you must've been at the meeting too.
- I didn't even bother registering.
- What?
My life's kept me on my toes.
You were on your toes?
Isn't that all the more reason to attend?
- Anyway, you didn't attend?
- No.
I wasn't desperate for money,
so I didn't bother registering.
Instead, I handled other matters.
Understood.
So, while the four of them
were in the same place,
you were handling personal matters.
Anyway, starting now,
you will assist me
in identifying the culprit.
You will investigate the scene
in teams of two.
- To prove your innocence,
- What a nuisance.
you must catch the culprit. Got it?
I will find out who did this
to avenge my friend.
How will we be paired up?
You want me to pair you
with your friend?
(NO, WITH GOLD SPOON♥)
You've got to be kidding me.
I'll give you what you want.
Take your friend with you.
- Let's do our best with the investigation.
- Sure.
Shall we?
I can't believe what happened.
The business owners
are worried sick as it is.
EXAMINING THE SCENE
THE NIGHT OF AUGUST 12, 2020
SOCIAL DISTANCING
AND HEAVY RAIN
GANGDAM STATION'S YOUTH STREET
WAS ALL BUT EMPTY
MEANWHILE
IN AN EMPTY LOT
THE VICTIM WAS FOUND DEAD
EMPTY LOT, LEE GUN-JUN'S HOUSE
JANG C-STORE'S CONVENIENCE STORE,
GANGDAM POLICE AGENCY, HANSIM POCHA
GANGSTER WHOLE CHICKEN, CLUB SLAM
HA GOLD SPOON'S OFFICE, SENSIBILITY BAR
INITIAL EXAMINATION OF CRIME SCENE
COLLECT CLUES FOR 15 MINUTES IN PAIRS
- C-store.
- Yeah?
You botched my shot
at getting paired up with Gold Spoon.
I'm struggling enough as it is,
and now a person's dead.
We'll have even fewer people
in the streets at night now.
Tonight's the night.
I'll look into every angle.
TEAM 3: JANG DETECTIVE & PARK CHICKEN
So, Gun-mi was a man, huh?
We'll start by checking that first.
AN EMPTY LOT IN THE CORNER
OF GANGDAM STATION'S YOUTH STREET
GANGDAM DISTRICT
TEMPORARY SCREENING CENTER
A TEMPORARY COVID-19 SCREENING CENTER
IS SET UP IN ONE CORNER
CONSTRUCTION MATERIALS
ARE SCATTERED EVERYWHERE
The body was found in an empty lot.
Due to the rain,
the bloodstains and other evidence
had already been washed away.
It's possible that the culprit's traces
were washed away as well.
I don't think this case
will be an easy one to solve.
That little...
Oh no, my poor Gun-mi.
Man, what a shame, Gun-jun.
Gun-jun, was it?
The kid had me completely fooled.
I thought she was a woman.
How was I supposed to know otherwise?
Is that why she always wore a scarf?
That explains the scarf.
- Detective, doesn't her neck look chafed?
- Hold on.
Isn't that a strangulation mark?
You're right. There's some redness.
Considering the mark,
she was likely strangled to death.
Look at her head.
She has a deep gash on her head.
- You're right.
- That's pretty deep.
It looks like it was made
with a claw hammer.
What's this?
What happened here?
Did something chafe her back?
Doesn't it look like
something was scraped against it?
Are these scratches from fingernails?
What are these marks?
She also has wounds
on the back of her hands.
It clearly got physical.
It's safe to say she was in a fistfight.
- She's pretty banged up.
- Exactly.
What could've been the murder weapon?
Was she attacked with a shovel?
This shovel...
DID HE FIND THE MURDER WEAPON?
Goodness. What do we have here?
- Hey, C-store.
- Yeah?
Aren't her shoes too clean?
It could be because of the rain.
- Were the soles washed clean?
- It could've washed the soles clean.
Let's check her purse.
EXAMINING THE VICTIM'S BELONGINGS
There's quite a bit of stuff here.
Jeez, this is a lot.
A passport? Was he going somewhere?
Why else would he have a passport on him?
Why was she carrying around a passport
when she's never even
traveled abroad before?
She's been making a lot of money.
"Kim Sucker, Lightweight,
Richie, Han Sucker."
She got a lot of money
out of these suckers.
She also got her deposit back,
so she must've been planning to move out.
I guess she was planning to
leave the country.
- Probably to run away abroad or something.
- What's this?
FUNGMU AIR, E-TICKET
She booked a flight to Russia.
Russia?
She was going to take the redeye tonight,
but missed the 11:59 p.m. flight.
LEE GUN-JUN'S PHONE
What is it?
- She had been texting.
- About what?
It was with Jang C-store,
the convenience store part-timer.
C-store, you little punk!
What are the texts about?
MESSAGES
She wrote, "Hope you're ready."
"Hope you're ready"?
C-store called her at 9:57 p.m.
What the hell? C-store, you little...
Mr. Attorney, I see you've exchanged
messages with Gun-jun.
MESSAGES WITH HA GOLD SPOON
"How about a drink?"
"I'm in. When?"
"How's today?"
"Meet me at my usual lounge bar."
Who says we can't be friends?
- And here I thought you were a decent guy.
- There's nothing to it.
Besides, we didn't meet up.
You didn't?
THE VICTIM'S WALLET
ID CARD
She had a fake ID for Lee Gun-mi.
OFFICIAL ID: LEE GUN-JUN
FAKE ID: LEE GUN-MI
Gold Spoon's one generous man.
This 50-million-won check
was issued by Ha Gold Spoon.
Mr. Attorney.
- Yes?
- This is awfully suspicious.
Well...
- I knew her as Gun-mi.
- Smile.
MR. SUSPICIOUS ATTORNEY
That's a great shot.
Goldspoon Buildings 1 and 2.
Why did a guy who owns two buildings
do such a thing?
HA GOLD SPOON'S OFFICE
LET US HELP WITH THE LEASE DISPUTE
CAUSED BY COVID-19!
GANGDAM DISTRICT
LEASE DISPUTE CONSULTATION CENTER
OPERATING AS A CONSULTATION CENTER
FOR THE GANGDAM DISTRICT LEASE DISPUTES
HA GOLD SPOON'S OFFICE
"Department of Business Administration."
"Master's Program at the School of Law."
"Illyu University School of Law
Graduation Ceremony."
Is that his father?
GRANDFATHER, FATHER
What's this?
Gucci and Louis Vuitton.
LUXURY ITEMS RECEIVED AS GIFTS?
"The support fund will be a big help
when you run for the National Assembly."
"Remember who got you this far,
and don't screw up."
"Stay focused, and don't screw up."
What's all this about not screwing up?
"Don't screw up."
"Don't embarrass your father..."
These must be from his father.
A JOURNALIST AT SPRINT NEWS
WILL PUBLISH AN ARTICLE, SO DON'T SCREW UP
Sprint News, huh?
"A Meeting With Business Owners
Impacted by COVID-19 Is Underway."
"After Ha Mediator became aware
of the business owners' difficulties..."
How did Gold Spoon
come up with such a good idea?
This guy's not so clean, is he?
BUSINESS CARDS FROM FANCY BARS
He goes to the bar run by Xi Manager,
the one run by Jeong Tender,
and even the one run by Kim Piano Key.
No wonder I liked him.
"Sensibility Bar."
BUSINESS CARD FROM ANOTHER BAR FOUND
That's where Gun-mi used to work.
He sure loves to drink for an attorney.
DOES THE PRIVILEGED RICH MAN
ENJOY THE NIGHTLIFE?
What's that?
CRUMPLED PAPER IN THE TRASH CAN
You've got to be kidding me.
She thinks a slap to her forehead
cured her text neck?
"Do you believe there's a god,
Gold Spoon?"
"Well, I do.
Be my savior and my god, Gold Spoon."
It looks like Dancer has it bad again.
FROM GOLD SPOON'S PRINCESS, AN DANCER
What the heck? What's this?
Why are all the nostrils heart-shaped?
What's this guy's deal?
Why does he keep photos like these?
A DOCUMENT ENVELOPE INSIDE THE DRAWER
A non-disclosure agreement
signed by Bang Libertine.
"Duty of confidentiality,
non-disclosure,
and compensation of five million won."
"Bang Libertine."
"Shin Fox."
"Park Hyeon-jun."
WHAT MUST BE KEPT SECRET?
Let's see.
HA GOLD SPOON'S PHONE
Let's check his messages.
"I'm Ha Gold Spoon,
the one you met at Sensibility."
"Then tell me which days you're free."
Is Gold Spoon serious?
"Park Hyeon-jun, convenience store."
Wait. What's this?
PARK HYEON-JUN/CONVENIENCE STORE
I read these messages
on Lee Gun-mi's phone earlier.
What the heck?
"Memories of that day."
They slept together.
Mr. Attorney!
Mr. Attorney,
I didn't expect this from you.
I must admit, I'm a little disappointed.
You must've been into clubbing.
VIBING
Hey, don't mess with that.
That's reserved for the DJ!
Come on, it's me you're talking to.
It's not like I haven't been here before.
HA GOLD SPOON IS NO STRANGER TO CLUBBING
I want to check out the club you work at.
I was rejected at the door
the last time I went there.
I think I know why. It's because...
- Never mind.
- Why? Tell me.
- Forget it.
- Tell me.
Come here. Just tell me, will you?
How could I?
CLUB SLAM
Why's this door locked?
- What? It's over here.
- Hey, friend.
The entrance is this way.
What?
What's this door, then?
What are you talking about?
Find your own way in.
A DOOR WITH A LOCK?
HEADING TO CLUB SLAM'S ACTUAL ENTRANCE
I got bounced at the door once
when I tried to get in.
I've made it my mission
to get inside a club at least once.
CONGRATULATIONS!
JANG C-STORE ENTERS A CLUB
I'd give anything to write my name
on a sign-in sheet.
Why won't they let me into these places?
August 8th.
Lee Gun-mi, a 27-year-old,
entered the club.
Wasn't she friends with Dancer?
An Dancer's break room.
SET UP IN THE CORNER OF THE CLUB
A BREAK AREA FOR DANCERS
AN DANCER'S LOCKER
I see she wanted to be a K-pop idol.
ALWAYS DO A FIT CHECK!
YOU'LL BE AN IDOL ONE DAY
I'LL EVEN HAVE A MANAGER WHO FANS ME
HOW DID AN ASPIRING IDOL
END UP AS A DANCER IN A CLUB?
An Dancer's phone is here.
AN DANCER'S PHONE
AN DANCER'S CALL LOG
She talked to Kim Club for 22 seconds.
She called Lee Gun-mi at 9:51 p.m.,
talked to Kim Club at 10:05 p.m.,
and called Lee Gun-mi again at 10:55 p.m.
She talked to Lee Gun-mi at 9:20 p.m.
and called her at 9:51 p.m. and 10:55 p.m.
She called,
but the calls didn't go through.
Lee Gun-mi, on the 12th.
"I'll be outside Slam
at 9:30 p.m. with the money."
"Gun-mi, we're still on for later, right?"
"I'll be at Hansim Pocha.
Call me when you get here."
"Why can't I reach you?
You're coming, right?"
"Is something up? Where are you?"
"How dare that tiny bitch...
KIM CLUB
...threaten to sue me?"
"If I ever catch you
with that fraud again,
I'm going to kill you."
"Okay."
"Mr. Kim, I have something important
to tell you after work."
"As if you could have anything
important to say."
There was bad blood between them, huh?
TINY BITCH, FRAUD
I'm no good with social media,
but here I am.
AN DANCER'S INSTAGRAM
"Catching a drink with Gun-mi after work."
"Gun-mi's being harassed
by a crazy woman."
SAYS SHE WON'T EVEN EAT
FRIED CHICKEN ANYMORE...
MAN OR ALIEN, I DON'T CARE!
YOU HAVE MY SUPPORT ♡
Not even eating fried chicken, huh?
So Park Chicken is who she meant
by crazy woman.
A PHOTO STRIP
Oh, right. She said
she was friends with Lee Gun-mi.
This was ripped apart
and taped back together.
Did they have a falling out?
What's this?
Isn't this a camera?
A TINY CAMERA?
(DISCOVERS SOMETHING MORE)
What's this?
"Lee Eighty"?
"China... Korea... A branch"?
"An idol singer in China.
One billion, five hundred million."
Who's Lee Eighty?
What am I reading? What does this mean?
What's with these flyers from China?
Is she headed there
to entertain VIP customers?
"Contract Termination."
Wait a second. Contract termination?
"I, An Dancer..."
AS OF TODAY, I, AN DANCER, SETTLED MY DEBT
OF 500 MILLION WON IN A SINGLE PAYMENT...
That's incredible. Good for you, Dancer.
Okay, what's next? What's this card?
"Secret Card"?
What secret card?
I should check out Kim Club's office.
KIM CLUB'S OFFICE
From what I've observed so far,
that guy is a menace.
I decided to search his office
because I found him suspicious.
FILE FOLDER ON THE DESK
"Contract."
"Lee Performer hereby
enters into this contract."
Lee Performer signed this in 2015?
Wait. Lee Performer had plastic surgery?
Did he put Lee Performer to work
after making them get plastic surgery?
An Dancer...
This is shocking.
No wonder I wasn't attracted to her.
You little punk.
You should always start
by searching places like this.
I knew it.
AS PREDICTED
Jang Detective's sixth sense!
"VIP Party Log"?
Wang Chaebol, Gae Politician, Na Star.
Even Ha Gold Spoon
has been attending these VIP parties.
Seriously?
Why did he write my name in this?
CALENDAR ON THE DESK
"Fuzz, fuzz, fuzz"?
As in the police? Are these the dates
of when they're raiding?
VIP parties, VIP...
There's a key card.
ANOTHER SECRET CARD?
C-store.
C-STORE'S BEAMING
NOW THAT HIS DREAM CAME TRUE
What's up with you?
Did you find something?
(HOLDING UP HIGH)
- What's wrong with him?
- What's this?
I don't know.
DOES THE SECRET CARD OPEN THIS DOOR?
BINGO!
What's this?
HIDDEN BEHIND THE LOCKED DOOR
A SECRET SPACE
The club has a secret den.
No way. The bottles of liquor here
are all older than I am.
My gosh. What is all this?
WHOA!
No way.
100 grams of meat for 4.5 million won?
Ice for 28 million won?
This can't be actual ice.
Should I report this to the police?
I'd better go do that.
Officer, I saw something really important.
You should check it out over there.
I cannot answer you.
You don't have to answer me.
But if you go check it out,
you'll get praised for doing a good job.
So this is the police station.
LIEUTENANT GU LACKEY
TRUSTWORTHY POLICE, A SAFE COUNTRY
"Flood-Related Road Closures."
"From 7 p.m. to 10:15 p.m."
"From Goldspoon Building
to Hansim Pocha."
GOLDSPOON BUILDING 1, HANSIM POCHA
BETWEEN GOLDSPOON BUILDING 1
AND HANSIM POCHA
THE SECTION WAS BLOCKED OFF
DUE TO FLOODING
NO ENTRY
DETOUR ADVISED DUE TO ROAD FLOOD
Goldspoon Building 1 was blocked off
between 10:15 and 10:30 p.m.
11:15 P.M., YOUTH STREET
GOLDSPOON BUILDING 1 - HANSIM POCHA
"Under repair."
The computer's being repaired?
What's this now?
WAIVER OF PUNISHMENT (SETTLEMENT)
Not again, Ms. Chicken.
"Park Chicken, Gu Ninety."
"The victim, Gu Ninety,
was offered a whopping 20 million won
and came to an amicable agreement."
I see.
Why did Ms. Chicken
get mixed up in something like this?
GANGSTER WHOLE CHICKEN
WHOLE CHICKIN
It's whole "chicken", not "chickin."
"We only fry a limited number
of 50 chickens each day."
WE'RE NOT ON FOOD DELIVERY APPS.
WE DELIVER OURSELVES.
Jeez, look at all the blood.
That's real blood.
Does she really slaughter
the chickens herself here?
That's intense.
There's a chicken coop right here.
She actually raises her chickens here.
That's insane.
THE ALLEY NEXT TO GANGSTER WHOLE CHICKEN
LOCATED AT THE END OF THE ALLEY
GANGSTER WHOLE CHICKEN
RECYCLING STATION
PARK CHICKEN'S ROOM
IN A CORNER OF THE RESTAURANT
INSIDE A STORAGE BOX
"Strong Punch, Fire Fist Award."
I knew she packed a punch.
She's the former female champion.
HER FIERY PAST
Here we go. I found something.
It's a document envelope.
"Medical Report."
Her rotator cuff was torn.
That's why she had to quit boxing,
and that led to her contract
being terminated.
In 2015, her agent, Bok Punch,
terminated her contract.
"Seoul Unfair Police Station."
What's this about?
What? Hold on.
I'LL GET YOU MYSELF!
Of course. Now we're in business.
JANG PRIVATE INVESTIGATOR
EVERYTHING YOU WANT
ON THE FRIED CHICKEN RESTAURANT COUNTER
Park Chicken.
PARK CHICKEN'S PHONE
"Go live your life now.
Report if you hear from the boss."
That was in 2015, so five years ago.
"Got it."
She reached out once a year.
"Lee Eighty." Hold on.
I saw that name on a business card.
Could it be that Chinese person?
"I told Lee Eighty
to come to the empty lot."
Lee Gun-mi, Park Chicken, and An Dancer
are all connected in some way.
Gun-jun, where were you headed
in such a hurry?
ON THE 2ND FLOOR
OF THE CONVENIENCE STORE BUILDING
VICTIM LEE GUN-JUN'S HOUSE
First of all, I have to look into Gun-mi,
or more precisely, Gun-jun.
I'll search this place from top to bottom.
"Studio Apartment Rental Contract."
"Electricity Service Termination Notice."
THE RENTAL AGREEMENT ENDED
BEFORE THE DAY OF THE MURDER
He must've been in a real hurry.
BELONGINGS SCATTERED EVERYWHERE
I doubt this was an easy life,
with all these wigs and fishnets.
ALL SORTS OF ITEMS
USED TO DRESS UP AS A WOMAN
Hold on.
Why is this blouse cut up?
What's that about?
Why was it cut precisely in half?
Nothing in the cup.
Why is there no photo in here?
AN EMPTY PICTURE FRAME
LEE GUN-JUN'S LAPTOP
"E-ticket Itinerary..."
It's Darkscene.
No connection.
CURRENTLY OFFLINE
"E-ticket Itinerary and Receipt."
DEPARTURE: SEOUL/INCHEON
ARRIVAL: MOSCOW
Moscow?
What's this?
Is this gasoline?
Oh, that's definitely gasoline.
Why did she have so much gasoline at home?
WALLET INSIDE THE SUITCASE
A written apology by Kim Club.
October 30, 2000. Kim Club.
A WRITTEN APOLOGY BY KIM CLUB?
NARCOTICS CRIME INVESTIGATION TEAM 1
SERGEANT KIM CLUB
Of course.
I knew there was more to Mr. Kim.
What will I be able to find
In the convenience store?
GS25 GANGDAM STATION BRANCH
THE CONVENIENCE STORE
JANG C-STORE WORKS AT
There's definitely something off
about C-store.
He said he knew
Lee Gun-jun from high school,
so I'm guessing
there's some history between them.
What kind of family photo is this?
Judging by how angry the dad looks,
C-store clearly caused some trouble.
That little brat.
What sort of dolls are these?
What are they?
I don't get it.
Why does he have such unusual dolls?
They all have long hair,
almost like women.
And they're all holding umbrellas.
A PRIVATE AREA FOR JANG C-STORE
IN A CORNER OF THE STORE
The 27-year-old.
Jang C-store.
Look at that.
I already got something.
"Man Stabs Stranger in Random Killing
in Maniac Province."
"Random, random, random."
"A man in his twenties fled
after pouring boiling oil
on a five-year-old."
"A man in his twenties."
"A, a man in his thirties."
Why does he have these news clippings?
"Ruling, Jang C-store."
"Ordered to be placed
in juvenile detention"?
C-store was the perpetrator?
I see.
C-store bullied Lee Gun-jun.
This is a case of school violence.
WAS JANG C-STORE A SCHOOL BULLY?
Who would've thought, huh?
Wait, the trash can.
I forgot to check the trash can.
What's this?
SOMETHING BROKEN?
A CCTV?
Why is it smashed?
A BROKEN SECURITY CAMERA
What's this?
What did he do with this?
HAMMER
HANSIM POCHA
This is where everyone gathered.
GANGDAM STATION YOUTH STREET MEETING
A meeting was held at Hansim Pocha,
and four of the five suspects
were present.
I need to find out
if they were all there the entire time.
So they had to choose between
a tiered payment according to annual sales
or an equal lump sum payment.
The lump sum payment won more votes.
REGISTRATION FORM FOR MEETING WITH
BUSINESS OWNERS AFFECTED BY COVID-19
WED, AUGUST 12, 2020, 9:30 P.M.
SUBMIT REGISTRATION FORM
TO THE CONSULTATION CENTER
ONLY APPLICANTS ARE ELIGIBLE
TO RECEIVE THE SUPPORT FUND
LIST OF ATTENDANTS
♪ PLEASE SIGN BELOW WHEN LEAVING
Right. Kim Club attended.
An Dancer attended as a proxy.
Jang C-store filled in
for Hong Father-in-law.
He didn't sign out.
(EMPTY SIGNATURE FIELD)
"Useful information on COVID-19 damages
affecting small businesses."
"Joo, the tenant of store A
on Youth Street in Gangdam District,
had their business suspended
for operating illegally at night."
What's this?
SENSIBILITY BAR
Hold on a second.
All right, let's take a look.
THE BAR WHERE THE VICTIM,
LEE GUN-MI, WORKED
Sensibility Bar is closed.
It received a two-week suspension penalty.
"Due to a violation
of the Infectious Disease Control
and Prevention Act."
How do I get in?
All the doors are locked.
None of them opens.
- Mr. Ha Gold Spoon, you must leave now.
- Right.
I'm right behind you.
Have you already forgotten
how kind I was to you last week?
Give me five more minutes.
No exceptions, sir.
- No exceptions?
- You need to go.
By the looks of it,
I should just escort you to jail.
Me?
Never mind.
You'd better watch what you say.
I was just messing around.
People were way shadier than I expected.
INITIAL EXAMINATION
OF CRIME SCENE CONCLUDED
COMBINE THE CLUES
During this briefing,
I want you to ask all your questions
and answer any questions directed at you
as best as you can.
We'll begin with Ms. Dancer.
Why don't you kick us off?
Sure thing.
FIRST BRIEFING: AN DANCER
I wonder where she's been poking around.
First things first,
I'd like to talk about the body.
The wound on her head stood out the most.
Whatever caused it left a deep gash.
That's why I believe the blow to the head
caused Ms. Gun-mi's death.
Why use such a formal address
to talk about your friend?
Because this is a formal setting, C-store.
Why can't you tell
when to speak and when not to?
Aren't you old enough to know better?
She said it was a formal setting,
yet she still called me C-store.
- You two are friends.
- What's that about?
- Let's--
- You're still alive.
Let's keep it professional.
All right, moving on.
The marks on her neck
suggested she had been strangled.
Agreed.
- Also--
- She was all banged up.
Exactly. Especially her arms.
The cuts and bruises there could
only have been caused during a scuffle.
But here's something suspicious.
The soles of her shoes were too clean.
Even accounting
for the rain washing them off,
wouldn't there be
some sort of trace left behind
after such a violent fight?
The soles were too clean?
- They were too clean.
- Did someone change her shoes?
One more thing.
- There's the brick.
- The brick?
I found a brick with blood on it.
A bloody brick?
Yes, I found a brick
stained with a lot of blood.
There's a possibility
she was struck on the head with it.
I don't think so.
That's just what I think.
- Okay.
- Right.
Moving on.
The next person I'm curious about is...
That look on her face
makes me uneasy again.
When else would I get to
go into Gold Spoon's room?
- I'm already uncomfortable.
- She went through everything.
She took advantage of this chance
because she likes him.
She wouldn't be smiling like that
if she had properly searched his office.
- I did find something a bit suspicious.
- I see.
- What is it?
- A bit suspicious?
What was the nature
of your relationship to Gun-mi?
What?
You two were exchanging texts
like you had a thing going on.
Didn't you say
you just met her at the bar?
You guys were texting each other?
It's not so unusual to exchange numbers
with someone you clicked at a bar, is it?
You hit her up first.
I just asked to meet, that's all.
Explain these, then.
Heart-shaped nostrils!
"Heart-shaped nostrils"?
Is this why
I don't do it for you, Gold Spoon?
Jeez, well...
-"Heart-shaped nostrils"?
- To give you more context,
he kept photos of heart-shaped nostrils
hidden under his keyboard.
I mean, everyone has
a favorite body part, no?
- Not really.
- But nostrils?
- Who likes nostrils?
- Come on.
When you meet someone,
what makes you fall in love with them?
You can fall for someone's eyes,
personality, or voice.
Sure, but not nostrils.
- Well, I--
- Anyway, you have a thing for nostrils.
- I just--
- To each their own.
- I wasn't going to say this, but listen.
- Let me see your nostrils.
Have you ever wondered
why some mayo bottles
have a star-shaped tip?
Oh, yeah.
Have you ever imagined air coming out
of your nose in the shape of a heart?
- How beautiful is that?
- I suppose.
He got all misty-eyed. He's serious.
- Gold Spoon.
- Do we really need to
put my personal preference on trial
in front of everyone?
Gun-mi also had heart-shaped nostrils.
- I should check the nostrils later.
- To be honest,
I couldn't sense any love
in the air that came out of your nose.
- What about Lee Gun-mi?
- Breathe out your nose, not your mouth.
Did you feel love from her breath?
It was overwhelming.
Let's move on from that for now.
I noticed you were a regular
at Sensibility Bar.
You even brought back lighters.
- I wasn't a regular.
- There was a business card too.
You clearly go to bars often.
Do you enjoy the nightlife, Gold Spoon?
His family has three generations
of attorneys or something, right?
- That's what he said.
- Won't they lose face if word gets out?
My grandfather
was the Minister of Justice,
and my father was the prosecutor general
of the Seoul Central District
Prosecutors' Office.
As you know, I care deeply about
the local economy of Gangdam District.
- That's true. He's a brilliant man.
- I sometimes go to bars
to get insight into the reality
of self-employed people.
- Besides, I'm still young.
- What an excuse you've got.
He goes to the hottest places though,
like the bar run by Kim Piano Key.
Is it still in business?
They say it's a great place for singing.
Kim Piano Key
- I hear he's a pervert.
- Stop bringing up stuff like that.
Anyway, Gold Spoon,
your father must've found out
what you were up to.
Don't screw up.
- Don't screw up!
- Don't screw up.
Gold Spoon, don't screw up!
You get that a lot, don't you?
You need to get into politics,
so you were told not to screw up.
"Don't embarrass your father.
Don't screw up."
What he meant was that
I should take each step with care.
He wasn't trying to set me straight
because I had screwed up in any way.
I also found non-disclosure agreements.
Those who signed them
had to keep conversations
or their relationship with you a secret.
- And who signed them?
- And--
Shin Fox, Bang Libertine,
and Park Hyeon-jun.
- Those were their names.
- So, women?
Most sound like women's names,
but Park Hyeon-jun sounds like a man's.
Wait, so were you
in a romantic relationship with them?
Well, I'm not married.
I have both time and money,
so I can date whoever I want.
Do you swing both ways?
Gender isn't important.
- I date whoever I'm attracted to.
- Oh, so it doesn't matter to you.
- Gender doesn't matter?
- Does it not matter to you too?
I guess that's possible for some.
I can be drawn to anyone,
and that can sometimes leave me
vulnerable to people
who want to exploit my wealth.
- So that's why.
- He's an attorney for sure.
It's to keep them quiet
if they change their minds later.
- It's like an insurance, huh?
- You could say that.
- Detective, here's what I want to know.
- Go on.
Was he dating Lee Gun-mi
or Lee Gun-jun?
That's a good question.
I'm curious about that too.
In your messages with Park Hyeon-jun,
there was a photo of you two in bed,
topless and under the covers.
It must've been chilly.
Tell us about the unforgettable
memories of that day, Gold Spoon.
You sure looked like you had a good time.
I'll cover my ears.
- Did you sleep with him?
- He's looking away, avoiding eye contact.
- I'll tell you.
- Did you sleep with him?
I had a drink
- and passed out.
- As if.
Didn't I explain
the non-disclosure agreements?
That man in the photo
stole the document from me.
While you were out cold, huh?
Gold Spoon.
Go on.
I have shocking evidence.
- What is it?
- Is that so?
The man in the photo
looks very much like Gun-mi.
Is this Gun-mi?
Who is he?
Let me back you up with what I found.
- Sure.
- This was on Gun-mi's phone.
Didn't you catch this?
I didn't.
I found text messages on the phone
- I read those texts too.
- that was on her body.
In Mr. Gold Spoon's phone,
the name was saved as Park Hyeon-jun.
However,
an identical string of texts
was found on Gun-mi's phone.
Do you see where I'm going with this?
I'm afraid you're going to have to
give us an explanation.
Gun-mi and I had agreed to meet.
But after a while,
she began playing hard to get.
Right.
She kept turning down plans to meet,
so I got upset.
By now, you all know
why I was drawn to her.
Yeah, the nostrils.
That's when I met Park Hyeon-jun,
who looked a lot like Gun-mi
and had the feature I loved.
RAN INTO PARK HYEON-JUN
AT THE CONVENIENCE STORE
I felt drawn to him too.
So I asked for his number,
and we began exchanging texts.
But then you realized
they were the same person.
I had no idea.
- He was Gun-jun.
- You were duped twice.
It was Gun-jun all along.
Heart-shaped nostrils
can't be that common.
And of course, he'd use a fake name.
You and Gun-jun got into bed, and--
Before today, I had never even
heard of the name Lee Gun-jun.
- Hyeon-jun was Gun-jun.
- Park Hyeon-jun, then.
- Here's one last thing, Gold Spoon.
- Sure.
Did you ever throw away...
something important?
He likely threw it away
because it was trash. Come on, Dancer.
My love for you hasn't been crumpled.
What's that?
- The letter I wrote to him.
- You dug that out of the trash?
Did Gold Spoon crumple up
and throw away the love letter
An Dancer wrote him?
An Dancer doesn't have
heart-shaped nostrils,
but she wrote the letter
on a piece of heart-shaped paper.
All right, then.
I think it'd be best
for Gold Spoon to go next.
Before diving into the details,
I'd like to offer
a different interpretation
of the crime scene.
I can't take him seriously anymore
now that I know about his nostril fetish.
Here's the bloodstained brick.
Did anyone happen to see
the fan guard next to it?
- Yes, I saw the fan guard.
- I saw it too.
You saw it, right?
Now, focus on the marks on her back,
which follow an unknown pattern.
When I held the fan guard up to it,
I noticed the patterns matched.
So I made the assumption
that Lee Gun-mi
fell onto the fan guard first,
and someone came up and strangled her,
adding more pressure
and leaving those marks on her back.
And as for the order
in which the murder took place,
I believe she was first attacked
with the brick,
then strangled,
which left those marks on her back.
That's my theory about the crime.
Mr. Attorney sure is smart, isn't he?
Nobody else thought of that.
Mr. Club, I'm sure you're aware
that I'm not that fond of you.
- Excuse me?
- There's something sketchy about you.
- You're harsh with your employees.
- That came out of nowhere.
So I went to his office at the club
to dig up dirt on him.
But more so than Mr. Club,
Ms. An Dancer surprised me
with an unexpectedly dark past.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
I'm getting a headache. She's too much.
No, Dancer.
I told you to hold the heart up here.
- I think he kind of liked that.
- And breathe out of your nose.
Ms. An Dancer,
aren't you stuck in
an exploitative contract with Club Slam?
Come on, it's hardly exploitative.
Like I'd sign one with a mere dancer.
She's not even a K-pop idol.
Ms. Dancer, you were a trainee
at Star-Star Entertainment, right?
That's right.
When she signed with Club Slam,
her debt was carried over and increased
to a total of 550 million won.
That alone makes it
an exploitative contract.
On top of that,
one of the clauses
states that they could take measures
to make her look like her old self.
- Have you seen her old photos?
- Oh dear.
No, don't even bring them out.
Don't bring them out.
It's best not to see them.
Gold Spoon!
- Cover your eyes.
- Don't touch anything!
It's such a shame
that they butchered her pretty face.
An Dancer...
GASPING
What's this?
Is this what An Dancer looked like before?
- I thought it was you, Detective.
- Look, Detective.
- Your eyes are no good.
- I thought she looked amazing.
- I have a little question, Mr. Attorney.
- What is it?
What if she had that face
- but with heart-shaped nostrils?
- I've been wondering that too.
- Gold Spoon, is that all it takes?
- Would you date her or not?
Then I'd date her.
Really? Is the fetish really that intense?
- You should go back to your old self.
- It's my preference.
And while you're at it,
get your nostrils done too.
- Gold Spoon.
- All right.
I think it was the vanity.
That's where I found her phone.
These are some of her texts.
She and Mr. Club texted.
"Mr. Kim, I have something important
to tell you after work."
She sent that on August 12th.
I wondered what she wanted to
talk to him about.
You were halfway through completing
a contract termination.
Is that so?
- Dancer, is this true?
- I found the contents surprising.
It said that you repaid
the 500-million-won debt
in a single payment
- and demanded termination.
- That's right.
- She paid off her debt already?
- She didn't.
The only signature on it was hers.
- She was likely expecting a large payment.
- You think so?
- An Dancer.
- Yes?
Where were you going to
get the money from?
- I've got my own plans, Mr. Kim.
- Of course.
What I really want to know
is where she got the money
to settle her debt and request
to terminate her contract.
Then, I found this in her desk drawer.
You didn't have to be so thorough,
Gold Spoon.
She had flyers
and a business card from China.
- China?
- The name on it was Lee Eighty.
The note in the back read,
"1 billion, 500 million"
and something about debuting in China.
The tone was rather hopeful.
I couldn't tell what was on the flyers
because they were all in Chinese,
so I ran them through a translation app,
and I realized
they were VIP party exposés.
"The fall of the aristocracy."
"The disgraceful truth
behind elite political families."
The other one exposed
the top celebrity, Kang Pung-pung,
as a drug addict.
- And this.
- Yes?
You had a tiny camera.
- A camera?
- There was a camera
smaller than a table tennis ball.
By any chance,
were you planning to film me secretly
and sell the video to a Chinese broker?
Is that how you were going to
make the money?
- Well, I mean...
- Wait, you don't know?
The grown-ups are talking, all right?
I'm just...
Do you really not know?
- What is it? Tell us.
- The grown-ups are talking.
I'm just curious, that's all.
- Are you serious right now?
- Seriously?
Anyway, that's what I found out
about An Dancer.
- That'll be all.
- All right.
Should I go next?
- Sure.
- Go ahead.
NEXT BRIEFING: KIM CLUB
Mr. Attorney.
Me, again?
Did you check the wallet
on the victim's body?
- The wallet.
- I did.
Inside the wallet
was a check for 50 million won.
Wasn't that issued by Mr. Gold Spoon?
- It was.
- That's right.
It's likely that Lee Gun-mi
blackmailed him using
a photo of them together in bed.
That seems to be how she got the money.
I'm a victim too, guys.
- That came out of nowhere.
- That was unexpected.
- What's with the sudden 180?
- That 50 million won?
I should've paid five million won
and earned her silence,
but I failed to do that.
So I had to pay an additional 50 million.
PARK HYEON-JUN/CONVENIENCE STORE
I TOOK IT THAT DAY
If only it ended there, right?
But I'm sure it didn't.
And that usually leads to murder.
Fifty million won is just the beginning.
The grown-ups are talking!
HURT
Come on, C-store.
Look at C-store,
acting all innocent and naive.
- Why? I thought he was hardworking.
- I am.
Your past is quite different
from your present, C-store.
- Is that so?
- What? What do you mean?
- Turns out,
- Yes?
C-store spent a year in juvie.
- In juvenile detention?
- I knew it.
It's rare to be sent to juvie for a year.
He made Lee Gun-jun dress up as a girl
and bring him money.
He was the perpetrator.
- Man, what a piece of trash.
- So, it's like this.
So he knew about the victim's proclivity
and took advantage of it.
- That might not have even been the case.
- He's the worst, Detective.
He might not even have had
such a proclivity,
but the experience of making money
under such a disguise
could've led him to further pursue it.
You tell us.
Talk, you piece of trash!
How dare you move to our neighborhood,
acting like some innocent kid?
You can STFU.
- I didn't know you knew such a term.
- Is that the best abbreviation you know?
- C-store.
- I know a few.
What did I tell you
about how you talk to your elders?
- You brat.
- Let me explain.
You see,
back in the day,
I used to have some fun.
- Were you a bully?
- He was a short and skinny kid,
so we made him do things for us.
But I didn't know about this side of him.
I only found out today.
I had no idea that Gun-jun
spent part of his life as Lee Gun-mi.
- I swear.
- Is that so?
Detective, can I step in
and share something?
- I'm probably the only one who knows it.
- Sure.
As I said, Gun-mi and I
have been friends for a few years.
She appeared in Gangdam out of nowhere
after being gone for several years,
so I wondered why.
Then one day, she told me
- that she had to get revenge on someone.
- Revenge?
- Was this recent?
- Yes.
And she said she was going to
leave this place once she was done.
Is that so?
- Lee Gun-mi said that?
- Maybe it was this bastard.
- There's something off about him.
- I'll keep that in mind.
Anyway, I'm sure you all saw
the hole in the skull.
- Yes.
I found something that appears
to match the size and depth of the wound.
A claw hammer
was in the convenience store.
In the convenience store?
So the weapon wasn't the brick?
- That seems like the same size.
- It's the perfect size.
And here's more about his past.
Do you...
have a kid?
Look here.
Here's C-store in his school uniform.
Next to him is his girlfriend
who's also in a school uniform.
But that girlfriend is holding a baby.
Next to them in the photo
is an older man who looks very angry.
- They were teen parents.
- Teen parents.
I was clueless and didn't know better,
so I ended up becoming a dad
in high school.
But I took responsibility.
I've accepted responsibility
and stayed committed.
The older man in the photo
is my father-in-law.
He owns the convenience store.
Oh, it's your father-in-law's
convenience store.
- That's right.
- Really?
- No wonder.
- Oh dear.
And so--
No wonder he never took any days off.
- Do you still get paid?
- Of course!
I didn't understand what this was
because I didn't know who owned the store.
But his father-in-law
must've installed a security camera
to monitor him.
I found one in the trash
that had been smashed.
- Yes, I smashed the heck out of it
- You're a piece of work.
after finding it.
You're still just as hot-tempered.
He seems to have anger management issues.
Here's what I think.
He's been building up anger inside him
like a burning fire.
When I went through his desk,
I found news articles
on so-called random acts of violence,
including an incident
where boiling oil was poured on someone
and a random stabbing spree.
He had the news clippings
in his little collection.
Really?
Did you randomly attack
and kill Lee Gun-mi?
How can it be random
when we knew each other?
You didn't know Lee Gun-mi though.
You knew Lee Gun-jun.
- She's right.
- See? You just got caught in a lie, huh?
It could count as random
because you didn't know Lee Gun-mi.
That's not true.
- One more thing.
- Unbelievable.
I haven't quite figured this out yet,
but on the convenience store counter,
I found five dolls displayed in a row.
- Give me a break.
- They all had long, straight hair
and were holding umbrellas.
- A rainy day.
- Perhaps on a rainy day like today,
he kills someone and gets rid of a doll.
Or maybe he's adding one
- for every crime he commits.
- That may be the case.
You bastard. I've had it with you.
- Assume push-up position.
- My joints on my right side are weak.
Why do you have those dolls?
I just like them, that's all.
Why would you though? You're a guy.
Please be respectful
of people's preferences.
- Right.
- Sir, come on.
I guess it's better than a nostril fetish.
Of course. His fetish was shocking.
There are no lesser preferences.
- The neighborhood has such an awful vibe.
- All right, Detective.
That's all I have for now.
I'm disappointed in you, Mr. Club.
All right, then.
C-store, why don't you go next?
Sure.
Okay.
First of all,
I went to Mr. Club's club.
It was for one reason only.
You wanted to go inside, huh?
It was amazing. My only regret
is that I couldn't play some music.
Come straight to me next time,
and I'll get you past the bouncer.
Thanks, sir. Okay.
My next stop was Ms. Chicken's restaurant.
All you did at my club
was take a tour of the place?
Yes.
C-store,
assume push-up position.
This is a tough character to play.
I went to Ms. Chicken's restaurant,
and I was so shocked.
Ms. Chicken
used to be
a boxer.
I saw that too.
A former boxer?
- So she was a boxer?
- She was a boxer,
- but not just any boxer.
- Look at her posture.
In 2015,
she even won
the Strong Punch, Fire Fist Award.
So, why didn't her boxing career take off?
I wonder why.
- She had an unfortunate accident.
- Oh dear.
She tore her rotator cuff.
In her case, it was serious.
However,
she didn't consider this a mere accident.
She claimed that someone had drugged her
before the match.
Why? Because someone needed her to lose.
She accused someone of fixing the match
and asked the police
to launch a formal investigation.
However, the police claimed
that there was no evidence of her claims
and closed the case.
Then, she received the paperwork
stating as such.
RE: INVESTIGATION RESULTS NOTICE
- On it, she left a memo.
- What did it say?
-"I'll get you myself."
- I see.
- Unbelievable.
- What's wrong with that?
There are texts she exchanged with Gun-mi
after the case was closed.
What did they talk about?
-"So, what about your boss?"
- Okay.
There's a big time jump
after the first text.
She asked Gun-mi if she had looked into it
and confronted her for not reporting back.
Gun-mi appeared to be very stressed by it.
- Now, let's talk about this.
- Detective, hold on.
What was Gun-mi doing in 2015
for you to be interested in her boss?
She was the one
who injected the drug into my shoulder.
- Really?
- What?
Before the match, a girl bumped into me
and injected something into my shoulder.
After that, I couldn't punch.
I instinctively knew
she had done something,
so I confronted her after the match.
So, until then, you didn't know her?
I didn't.
- But...
- You're saying that someone
put Lee Gun-mi up to it.
Gun-mi said someone
had ordered her to do it.
So what next?
I told her to bring that punk to me.
That means the person
who ordered Lee Gun-mi to do it
was Lee Eighty,
as in the name on the business card.
Because she hired a private investigator...
Jang Private Investigator strikes again.
- Jang Private Investigator?
- Right.
She had Jang Private Investigator
look into Lee Eighty,
and he discovered that Lee Eighty
frequented our neighborhood.
- Lee Eighty?
- Yes.
Do you really think I opened a shop
in this neighborhood just to earn money?
I came here for Lee Eighty.
But then,
something unexpected happened.
What now?
You lost your temper again yesterday,
didn't you?
- What happened?
- What is it?
- She beat the crap out of someone.
- Oh dear.
This is what happened.
Shortly before the murder took place,
Ms. Chicken and the victim
settled for 20 million won,
when the victim was injured enough
to be hospitalized for eight weeks.
- Oh my.
- Oh dear.
He probably also thought
the amount was excessive,
given that he wrote
"a whopping" 20 million won.
I paid him well to get released quickly.
I didn't want the hassle.
- All right.
- Who did she assault?
The victim's name is Gu Ninety.
- Gu Ninety?
- She beat up Gu Ninety?
- Lee Eighty and now Gu Ninety?
- That's his name?
- Do they belong to the Hair-Parting Gang?
- I suppose.
So, that's not the same person
as Lee Eight.
- It's Lee Eighty, not Lee Eight.
- Right, Eighty.
- It's a completely different person.
- Lee Eight exists as well.
Anyhow, Lee Eighty.
Lee Eighty and Lee Eight
are completely different people.
Isn't Lee Eighty Chinese?
Fine, let me explain.
- Gun-mi said she had Lee Eighty with her.
- Okay.
- So I went and beat the crap out of him.
- Right.
But he turned out to be Gu Ninety!
- His hair was parted more to the side.
- It was 90% to the side.
- Oh dear!
But before I could do anything,
someone called the cops.
What else could I have done
but settle quickly?
There was no time to waste
if I wanted to catch Lee Eighty.
Okay, moving on.
Did any of you stop by the police station?
Not yet.
At the police station,
I found a list of roadblocks
that were set up at specific times
because of the flood.
The list shows
that the road between Hansim Pocha
and Mr. Attorney's building
was sectioned off.
Yes, that's right.
Didn't they block that section off
due to flooding?
The road was blocked once again
at 11:15 p.m.
Before that,
it was blocked until 10:30 p.m.
So there was a brief period
when it wasn't blocked.
Oh, so there was a period
when traffic wasn't restricted?
During that time...
Detective, now that I think about it,
if that road is blocked,
we have to take a detour
past the police station.
But there's always an officer
standing guard outside.
If the culprit didn't want to be seen,
they had to go through
the restricted area.
Can't you also go around the back?
That's something to think about.
Anyway, that's all I have for now.
CULPRIT'S ROUTE DEPENDS ON THE TIME
THE CRIME WAS COMMITTED
Now, let's hear from Ms. Chicken.
- Sure.
- Please go ahead.
I have a few follow-up questions for her.
Is using an animal's name
a family naming tradition?
Shut it.
WATCH YOUR MANNERS...
Since C-store came at me, I'll bite back.
I found texts between him and the victim
on the victim's phone.
Really?
At 9:05 p.m.,
C-store texted, "What's this?"
To that, the victim replied,
"Hope you're ready."
She knew something.
I doubt it was about a nice surprise.
That's exactly what it was.
It was a surprise?
What was it about? Tell me.
Don't stall and spill.
What made you say, "What's this?"
- A gift.
- What sort of gift?
- Just a gift.
- What was in the gift?
A gift.
Okay, whatever. Just cut the crap.
Why did you call her at 9:57 p.m.?
- Hey! Why did you call her at 9:57 p.m.?
- Sorry?
Well, I was curious.
- Did he call Gun-mi at 9:57 p.m.?
- C-store called her.
No one picked up.
Did you kill her for not picking up?
Come on. I don't kill someone
for not picking up my call.
I'm serious.
Anyway, I checked out the house
that Gun-mi,
or should I say Gun-jun, lived in.
She got a notice
about her electricity being cut off.
That, among other things,
suggested she was preparing to leave town.
She had only rented the house
for about a month, anyway.
She told me she came to get her revenge,
so maybe she was leaving because
she'd already done what she came to do.
Didn't you see the plane ticket
she had in her wallet?
- I saw it.
- There was one.
She booked a flight
- Bound for Russia.
- for 11:59 p.m. on the 12th.
- Right.
- For 11:59 p.m.?
I believe
this is somehow tied to the case,
so we should look into it.
Mister.
Me?
What did you do before running the club?
I used to work for a company.
What kind of company?
- I was a civil servant.
- A civil servant?
He used to be a fuzz.
What?
Oh, come on.
I was a detective, so what?
That's not a crime, is it?
- He was a crooked cop.
- So you were getting inside information.
I found an official apology
he wrote a while ago.
He was on the narcotics teams
at the Gangdam Police Station.
Yeah, I handled narcotics cases.
He worked at Gangdam Police Station
and carried out coercive investigations.
- Even back then, he had quite the temper.
- Right.
Anyway, I found
an official apology he wrote.
But do you know who had it?
Lee Gun-jun. He had it.
- What?
Lee Gun-jun had it.
How did he end up with a letter
you had written in 2000?
I found one more suspicious item,
but I'm not sure if it's related.
On Lee Gun-jun's desk at his place,
there was a picture frame
with a photo ripped out of it.
Only a ripped corner was left behind,
and you could see
what resembled the police logo.
So that got me thinking that maybe
Mr. Club was worried
about being connected to Gun-jun
and took the photo with him.
Were you ever in his room?
- This is embarrassing to say.
- Go on.
I met that girl
- while having drinks.
- Okay.
I wanted to start
a little something with her,
but when I woke up the next morning,
I noticed I had been robbed of everything
- at the hotel.
- I see.
- Unbelievable.
- And that tiny bitch had already left.
I'm guessing that's when she took
my wallet and the written apology.
- She took them all.
- And I guess she just kept them.
Why were you at Lee Gun-mi's house?
All I remembered about her was her name,
but despite my best efforts,
I couldn't find her.
But after several years,
she showed up at my club with An Dancer.
They were supposedly friends
and joined at the hip.
I knew I recognized her,
so I checked the sign-in sheet.
And it really was Lee Gun-mi.
Something felt off about her,
so I went to her place.
And what about the photo? What was it of?
I went to her place
and saw a family photo
with someone I recognized.
There was this colleague
from my days back in the force,
and she had a photo of his family.
What?
- A former cop colleague?
- Was she the daughter
of a former colleague?
You mean, son.
Was Lee Gun-mi in the photo?
The photo was taken a long time ago,
so I couldn't be sure.
So, there's a good chance
you worked with Lee Gun-jun's father.
Okay, that'll be all.
- Next, I'll move on to Ms. Dancer.
- Sure.
Your Story Highlights had captions
like "Eternal friendship"
and "Man or alien, I don't care."
But I guess you had a falling out,
because the photos you took on August 7th
had been ripped at some point.
- Yeah, right down the middle.
- Exactly.
That was the day
I saw Gun-mi
walk into Gold Spoon's office.
I had confided in her
about how I felt, you see.
I told her that I liked Gold Spoon a lot.
Even though she knew that,
she went into his office.
It's only normal
that it pissed me off, right?
Right, of course.
So, I said that was it for us
and ripped up the photo.
Why did you tape it back together?
- I was so mad, so I called her that night.
- Okay.
That's when I learned the truth.
She told me she was born a man
but had the heart of a woman.
And because of that,
she could never be with Gold Spoon.
At the time,
I didn't know Mr. Attorney's passion
for heart-shaped nostrils
trumped all else.
- Hold on.
- Yes?
When did you first meet Gun-mi?
Gun-mi?
She came up to me one day
when I was working at the club
and said I was pretty.
She was there as a guest?
Yes. She told me
she was my number one fan.
Once I learned we were the same age,
we became really close.
I do believe that they patched things up
because Lee Gun-mi texted her saying,
"I'll be outside Slam
at 9:30 p.m. with the money."
Dancer texted her multiple times,
but Gun-mi didn't respond
even after 9:40 p.m.
- Dancer couldn't reach her.
- So basically, no contact.
- Was she going to give her the money?
- Detective, this is what you must note.
The timeline of events
seems especially important today.
Why didn't the victim
reply even after 9:40 p.m.?
Mr. Gold Spoon said
- he last saw Lee Gun-jun at 9:45 p.m.
- Yes, 9:45 p.m.
C-store called the victim at 9:57 p.m.,
but the call was missed.
Again, the victim didn't pick up.
Please make note of that timeline.
Got it.
And here I thought
you were all fists and no brains.
All right.
FINAL BRIEFING: JANG DETECTIVE
Detective, did you find much?
The first question I have
is for An Dancer.
How did you end up working at Club Slam?
Me?
You saw what I looked like before.
It was really bad.
After ten failed auditions,
Star-Star Entertainment took me in.
They said I could make it
with some minor tweaks to my appearance.
That's how I ended up
getting a full body makeover.
They had me lose weight as well.
Since then, people have told me
I look like AN YUJIN of IVE.
I get that pretty often.
- No way. She's way prettier.
- You're like a half-baked version of her.
Who? IU?
- So? Is that when you got piles of debt?
- Anyway, moving on.
- I got the 400-million-won debt then.
- Because of the full body makeover?
It cost 400 million won?
- Jeez, just what did you get done?
- I can't say I'm surprised by that number.
Being reborn would've been quicker.
- The process was absolute hell.
- Really?
- They promised me a debut as an artist.
- Right.
But I wasn't aware of my debt until then.
When I thought my debut
was finally happening,
they showed me their books
and said I couldn't debut
until I cleared my 400-million-won debt.
How could I have that kind of money
when I spent most of my life as a trainee?
When I told them
I had no money to pay off my debt,
they told me to work part-time.
Have you heard of drop-offs?
It's what people do these days.
As in drug dealing?
I'd drop off a package somewhere.
- For someone to collect.
- Yes.
- That's what they made me do.
- What has the world come to?
Without 400 million won,
what option did I have? So, I did it.
But then, the police showed up.
THE POLICE?
So I went with them.
But instead of the police station,
they took me to a club.
There, Mr. Kim gave me two options.
Either I go to jail
- or work at the club.
- What a scumbag.
I chose to work at the club,
and 150 million won was added to my debt.
That was the cost of staying out of jail.
Hey!
- That was stated in the contract.
- You got a good deal, Dancer.
- You hear me?
- Thank you.
- Look at your old photos and reflect.
- Okay.
- That's how you ended up working at Slam.
- Yes, that's right.
The pieces are finally coming together.
At Mr. Club's office
inside the club he runs,
I obtained a list of VIP parties.
Our very own Mr. Gold Spoon
was also among the VIP guests.
I attended parties
held at a club in a building I own.
- Of course, he was there.
- What's wrong with that?
Influential politicians, business leaders,
and other prominent figures attended.
Everyone who's anyone shows up
at the VIP parties at my club.
Everyone's bound to show up
on a list or two if you dig like this.
Absolutely.
- Anyway,
- I'm jealous.
where is it that these people
enjoy their VIP parties?
I managed to find the very room
where the parties took place.
- You did?
- How did you get in there?
A key card?
ONLY A SECRET CARD CAN UNLOCK THE DOOR
Unbelievable.
Are you kidding me?
So this is what you've been up to.
Unbelievable.
They were doing drugs at these parties.
You've got to be kidding me.
Cocaine, meth,
- ecstasy, marijuana, and more.
- No, no.
There were all sorts of drugs in there.
Meat...
MEAT = MARIJUANA, CANDY = ECSTASY
- ...and others.
- Don't forget the candies.
The menu referred to drugs, didn't it?
ICE = METH
Oh, so that's how it connects.
You bastard.
I'm onto you now.
You people are worse than animals.
Mr. Gold Spoon.
- I didn't do drugs.
- You're not a privileged rich man.
- I didn't know.
- You're just an animal.
I didn't know they were there.
- I also have a question for An Dancer.
- Ask away.
Were you aware
of these so-called VIP parties?
- I was aware of them, yes.
- You were?
I know the adults are talking,
but can I add something to that?
Sure, go ahead.
He's scared he might get yelled at again.
- Detective, let's go easy on the kid now.
- He's so timid now.
- Let's go easy on the kid.
- Poor kid.
You've finally developed something
called manners.
Yes, it's definitely
made me more cautious.
Earlier,
Mr. Attorney mentioned
that he found Lee Eighty's business card.
- Yes. "One billion, five hundred million."
-"One billion, five hundred million."
Something about debuting in China too.
That money could be what Dancer would earn
by debuting in China,
but it might also be connected
to that tiny camera.
She might've recorded
the VIP guests partying
and traded the footage to settle her debt.
Hey, An Dancer.
Is that what you've been cooking
at my club?
- Just spill it.
- Were you going to rat us out?
First of all,
- I have a debt of 550 million won.
- Right.
Over the years,
I've only been able to pay off 50 million.
Yeah, 50 million won
over the course of 5 years.
That took me five years.
- At this rate--
- You only have 50 more years to go.
I confided in Gun-mi
about my financial problems,
and she told me what I could do.
Selling photos of VIP guests doing drugs
to people in China
could get me 500 million won per person.
Is Lee Eighty the name
of an entertainment agency in China?
No, Lee Eighty is a broker.
I had to hand him the photos to get paid.
Gun-mi also said she had found
a Chinese agency for me.
Dropping off drugs in the VIP room
was part of my job anyway,
so I made a hole in my purse like so.
- For the camera?
- I hid it here to take photos.
Doesn't Ms. Chicken also know Lee Eighty?
- No, she's been hunting him down.
- She's looking for him.
These two had been waiting for Lee Gun-mi
to find him and deliver him.
These two are connected to Lee Eighty.
- All right.
- We should try to find him.
Sounds good.
I have one last thing to ask.
- C-store.
- Yes?
You arrived at the meeting
for business owners at 10:10 p.m.
- I showed up late.
- At 10:10 p.m.
All attendees
had to sign out when leaving the meeting.
- That's right.
- Mr. Club signed out,
as did Dancer.
- She came as a proxy.
- Though she was representing someone else.
You had to sign the form
to receive the support fund.
Exactly. However,
not only did you show up late,
but you left without signing out,
even though
you could've received a support fund
for your father-in-law's
convenience store.
- His father-in-law...
- Why didn't he sign out?
Why didn't you sign out when leaving?
- He was furious when he arrived.
- Why were you so angry?
Here's the thing.
You said I was angry when I arrived.
- Yeah, while you were on the phone.
- I was on the phone.
I was on the phone
with our delivery guy.
Why were you angry at him?
He couldn't park his truck
in front of the convenience store
- because of the roadblocks.
- Right, they blocked the roads.
I suggested he park in a different spot,
but he said,
"If I do, the truck will block
the view of the CCTV."
You mean the CCTV
in front of Sensibility Bar?
Did he park there?
He probably did
and blocked the camera's view.
Detective, his statement just now
shouldn't be taken lightly.
Knowing when the CCTV
had been blocked seems crucial.
She's right.
- The camera outside Sensibility Bar.
- The truck, huh?
New evidence has surfaced
regarding the delivery truck.
- All right.
- The delivery truck.
THE DETECTIVE'S 1ST ROUND OF VOTING
I will cast my valuable vote.
My vote...
will go to the person
with a strong motive.
THE DETECTIVE CASTS 2 VOTES TOTAL,
1 OF WHICH IS CAST AFTER THE BRIEFING
Make a wise choice.
So that's where it was.
Detective, you'd better get this right
if you want to keep your badge.
IN MEMORY OF A CERTAIN DETECTIVE
WITH SWAGGER WHO WAS BANNED FROM THE FORCE
WHO WILL THE DETECTIVE VOTE FOR?
There's something this one person has
that the other four don't.
I'll tell you what that is.
WHO DOES JANG DETECTIVE
CURRENTLY THINK THE CULPRIT IS?
You have a family.
What does he mean?
A child.
You have a family.
JANG DETECTIVE CHOSE JANG C-STORE
What does he mean?
- A child.
- What?
You have a family of your own.
For goodness' sake.
I guess he has a point.
The youngest person here
has a wife and a child.
He even has a father-in-law.
This is why I can't stand old-timers.
Yet, you sounded like
a geezer yourself just now.
Anyway, let's all get back out there,
look for clues we missed,
and catch the killer.
Do better, damn it!
Reverting back
to your juvie days, are you?
That was intense.
Keep up the good work.
THE SCENE OF THE CRIME
WILL REVEAL THE CULPRIT
- Hello.
- How are you?
I bet he witnessed a lot of things.
Where should we even begin?
First of all,
I'd like to see what Mr. Club took.
- Oh, right.
- The photo.
- Show us the photo.
- I'd like to see the photo.
Mister, show us the photo
if you want to clear your name.
Tell us where you put it.
It's right here.
- You have it with you?
- Pull it out.
- I'll take it out.
- All right.
- This is the photo.
- The family photo.
Who's that?
It's Park Hyeon-jun!
Hang on a second.
That's Park Hyeon-jun.
- Park Hyeon-jun?
- I thought his name was Lee Gun-jun.
- That's odd.
It doesn't make any sense.
How can he be Park Hyeon-jun?
Then what about him?
Park Hyeon-jun was a guy.
Yeah, a guy.
- Wasn't that Lee Gun-jun's alias?
- Wasn't he also Lee Gun-jun?
Subtitle translation by: Yenny Kang